So people from the country with an eye, I can't say the name because I'm already shadow banned
beyond disbelief, are colonizing the Philippines. They are colonizing Argentina. There were all
these fires in Patagonia that turned out to be the land that President Javier has now given to
an entire contract for them. They are also doing consistent deed theft in Brooklyn and taking
homes from residents of Brooklyn that have been there for decades. They have also done similar
destabilizing of communities, particularly around schools in places like Lawrence, New Jersey and
Ramapo County, New York. And they are doing the same in the UK. They are running the mines in the Congo
where we are seeing resources consistently stripped and the people given nothing. They are buying
property to attain citizenship and financially backing prime ministers in the Caribbean.
So I'm going to connect some dots here. These people who believe in this ideology of apartheid,
of supremacy, who are carrying it out on multiple levels, as grand as G-side, as specific as school
systems, are taking over and have taken over entire governments of countries across the world.
These people who are currently supporting the death penalty for peace Indians, who have actively said
GDFs is not an issue and protect them in their home country. These people have also taken over the
government of the United States. And yet I have not heard a single Democrat who is trying to
vie for president. That's AOC. That's Corey. I want a Michigan fist! Booker, you know Kamala coming
through, Gavin Newsom. None of them have said anything is wrong with any of this. Then you have
the black Democrats, Roland Martin, and the rest of the people that be showing up on his show.
They don't make any mention of any of this. Nobody seems to think any of this is a problem.
Their actions, that they're taking over countries, even though these people are the ones funding
Donald Trump. And they try to act like he's the only problem, while actively choosing not to address
the real problem. So that means they're not courageous enough or willing to actually fix the
real problem. And if they're not, then why do they deserve your vote or your clicks?
Gotta be a better way!